Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
There’s no signal.
- Do you guys have signal?
- No.
Relax. We’ll be there in half an hour.
Why did we call off Bali?
This place doesn’t even exist on a map.
At least, we will appreciate what we have.
Haqi.
If you talk like an old man,
you won’t have friends at school.
You must be speaking from experience.
Excuse me?
I have lots of Instagram followers.
How many do you have?
You only have 200. I have a billion.
Hey, I’ve told you this before.
The man who raised me at the orphanage is very ill now.
That’s why we planned to visit him.
So you should know that not everyone has parents.
Look at your dad,
Even without parents he has a strong fighting spirit.
You should have that same spirit.
Then why didn’t you just adopt us?
I think it’s time.
They’re big enough to know.
Know what?
We’re not your real parents.
We adopted you all when you were little.
Oh no, so you’re taking us back to the orphanage?
Just kidding, Haqi!
- We’re kidding.
- It’s a joke.
I’m fine if I’m adopted.
Aww, my baby Haqi.
But it makes sense since Haqi doesn’t look like any of us.
Hey, Haqi is my most handsome son.
Dina, don’t say that.
Your grandmother once said I wasn’t pretty,
and until now I don’t feel pretty.
But Mom, if you keep telling someone that they’re pretty,
they will end up being overconfident like Dina!
Shut up! You’re overconfident!
- You think you’re so pretty.
- I am!
You--
Ouch!
What was that?
Is everybody okay?
- Haqi.
- I wanna see.
Just wait in the car.
Dad!
Nif, what was it?
Was it an animal?
Yes.
A deer.
Let’s go.
Get in.
Go get the boxes.
Okay.
Maman.
How are you?
Good.
Are you fine?
Yes, thankfully.
This is my wife.
Nadya.
Maman.
Haqi.
This is Sandi and Dina.
It’s been ages.
Yes, it’s been very long.
Haven’t been here in a while.
- This is Siti.
- Siti?
- My wife.
- Oh.
Hanif, Siti.
How are you?
Nadya.
Haqi.
What happened to your face?
Shush. Don’t be rude.
This is Dina and Sandi.
We’ve got some gifts from Jakarta.
It’s for the children, Man.
Thank you, Sir.
I’ll bring them inside. Let’s go inside.
Come on.
Thank God.
- Nif!
- Ton.
Nadya.
How are you?
You good?
Yeah, great.
Hanif!
Bro.
Hi, Nad.
Good to see you man.
- You keep getting bigger?
- You too.
How have you been?
Hi, how are you?
- Haqi.
- Hello!
Hi, beautiful.
Hello.
Hi.
Lets go in.
Let’s go.
- Honey?
- Hm?
Alright.
Auntie, you have a cold?
Come here, fist bump.
There’s no signal.
Stop using your phone.
We’re here again.
This time with friends.
Maman.
- Anton.
- How are you?
Good.
- Maman.
- Jef.
Maman.
Where are all the kids?
Two of them are here, Sir.
The rest have gone on a trip by bus.
They will be home tonight.
Why are you calling me ’Sir’?
Sorry, Nif.
Hasbi, Rani.
This is Uncle Hanif.
Hello.
Hasbi.
Rani.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull